Subtitles by
http://www.Downloadking2.Tk
The liver improves night ...
Because if so ....
you could never say  by taste.
Who are you?
Hello Archie.  Hello, dear.
You know this guy?
Sergeant Archibal Sparks  Dick knows.
Vic! Vic Trowbridge.
Hi Vic
You called last night, when
was in the shower?
Archie called yesterday  when
he was in the shower?
No, its reputation  remains intact.
Well, because this  It
is a little strange.
Who are you?
Military Police.  The Detention Unit.
Medideth Cole  I have learned.
Are you a soldier?
Not in my book,  Dressed out.
Insurance sergeant.
Hello dear, Vic,  Vai make coffee?
Coffee?
Ms. go to hell.
That had to be done  when
you were in the shower.
I just put some clothes.  Good idea.
Why do you chose?  I chose o.
It is a waitress at the bar.
It is a bad area,  I
just wanted a ride.
Sure.
She knew she was in her research,
needed a place to go.
What have you done?  Why run away?
After Cole found abandoned  the right to attack.
Absent without leave.
Assault with the hands.
Small lesions.
Quick escape.
Good night.
Thanks guys, I know it was
in the last minute.
Ok, Hello to your parents  and
I hope your dad is better.
Thank you. Merry Christmas guys.  Bye.
That should be speaker
fixed time ago.
Holidays are the time  to relax
the ethics of the world.
Merry Christmas Danny.
Other 9 hours happy.
I see that someone does
not  Christmas spirit.
Hey, Get It!
When told to find a  room ....
nobody said the bathroom.
Become  road captain.
And not have merit, but ....
a Christmas bonus.
Christmas bonus.
I try  trick?
Want a ticket?
Sure.  Almost.
Will this be good?
Already did.
The paper gift? What's Christmas?
Something. On Christmas.
Hello Polly, saw something
Yesterday, in the woods?
Yes, but I  I took care of that.
All passengers ....
honey, I promise you get?
before you wake up.
Until then, Ms. Thorp.  a dependent.
Okay, you can not eat ice cream.
Thank you very much. baby ....
ВЎPiece of junk!
Hey.  Wait your turn, please.
I just want to know if this
will leave  or go to Texas.
We can explain it.
Socio-Listen, I do not .....
Texas ВїDamn!
honey, what?
No honey, you can not Santa
bring a doll, you have one.
It sucks, but ....
Sometimes that happens.
Hold on.  Call-back, O.K?
The last call.  -The story of my life.
Here I go.
Ms. srs. And welcome aboard,
My name is Daniel ....
and be his driver in this
part  Travel ....
Picadelly your next stop is Texas
are 6 hours of travel ....
so sit back, relax  Christmas
and enjoy with us.
It is very interesting.
-Try this. It is more elegant.
Lavender Вї?
It is best used after bathing ....
but need something in the
morning  more ....
Cool.  -Exactly.
That's why we created
Sunburst line.
Nice.  Yes, it is pleasant.
Mr. Jerry Yarbro.  Re: Termination
of contract.
Besides not to follow District's
"zero tolerance "....
It is for my son, Stevie.
-It is Christmas.
Think is  appropriate?
No, just  the last minute.
Last minute is best  that afternoon.
Buying batteries?
Nobody cares  jacket while
operating the toy.
Is that it?  Yes
I saw before boarding the bus
it reached the alert.
I did not know that you spent
so much  effort to escape.
No, not escape, but
do something stupid.
How to escape  a red alert.
The Cinderella?
His grandfather was a Senator.
Shameful.
Only if  is found.
How many men are you?  -4 Informants.
The brigade Dick Chaney.  Why run?
Does it matter?
You know?  Overnight is good.
Take time to find  the girl.
I do not lose sleep.  OK --
No man should  is drinking alone.
What time do you get?
- Excuse me?
Your boots.  Station that Iraq?
You think I am the military?
You are not military.
He driver international
9 months in Baghdad.
Flames and we had hoped.
- Driven in 6th?
What is the 6th?
The last 6 miles andalucГ­a
Baghdad airport.
It is the most dangerous
section  the world.
The driver here  Max is crazy.
All aguГЎntense.
Be calm.
Anyone can see the signs
- What is it?
Gang colors.
Nots.
Awols are absent  without permission.
Great.
What does that mean?
Not Awols.  They are nomads.
Ok,  What does that mean?
A crowd of Satan.
You're looking for below No.
Sorry, but it seems that only  were
some idiots on their bicycles.
There is nothing that  concern. Care!
Stop the bus.  ВЎDetГ©ngalo!
Would you two to come,  me please?
The rest is here.
I coach football,  Yes first aid.
Check that.
I have no signal.  Does anyone have?
We are outside the area.
As in Iraq,  died around me.
Never tie.
Quiet.
Get help.  Let us help!
Hey, get the gun ....
Time to go!
They are the keys.  I got the keys.
Duke has.
Crap!
Bastard!
Come on, now!
Hey, come here!
You okay?
Okay?  Yes
Son of a bitch.
My God.
Hey, help me.
What do I do?  Make-pressure.
Press the wound.  Push!
Hold on.  My God!
Keys.  Where are ....
I suggest you go  the bus now.
Get out.
Move! Come on!
All aguГЎntense.
Wait, what about Duke?
We are not  moving.
Wait.  Stop!
It is an idiot, but  can not stop.
We will not  to stop.
Run!  Take my hand!
Close the door.  -Thank God.
Nena. -Let's talk later.
Approach.
Hey, what's your name?
Lindley, Walter Lindley.
Mr. Lindley is running 20
tons of steel, use it.
My God.
Someone knows something  medicine?
There is a first
-  help? Hold on.
No, I do not  need. I do.
We must stop the blood.
Are gauze or something?
I grazed a rib,  It is
a superficial wound.
Somebody has a damn tampon?  -I.
Thank you.  -God.
Place it around, set.
Trying to enter.
We are filming on the engine,
Who has a cell phone?
Call 911, the patrol  roads.
I tried, no service.
- Fuck Texas!
And the radius of the bus?
Does not work.
Crap! We gotta get out  the road.
If we stop we die.
You understand?  If we stop, we die.
There is an opening there.
Perhaps there is a people-there.
I see nothing.
- You take?
ВЎВїTake this route?
- For the love of God!
Care!
This path takes us  There
is no place for good.
Want to turn  honey and return?
Want to have your ass  the window?
I am not so  useless as you think.
Lower it.
Hey, speed,  are approaching.
I think  I control it.
There is a door!  -AtraviГ©sala.
ВЎAtraviГ©sala!
All bГЎjense the bus.
Is dead.  Move!
Hurry.
Hurry the hell!  Fast!
In the building!  Move!
Closed.
Somebody help me.
Well, we  completely screwed.
Yeah, better run!
Is closed. -Don 't stop.
It'sa end.
Get your car.  Come on.
Come on!
You rabbit.
- It's Duke!
Monitors back.
How-not, I'll do it.
We must raise this  Let us help.
Help me.
Coach, how are they called?
Yarbro, Jerry Yarbro.
How many bullets  Jerry are you?
Give me, let me see.
You should let him see,
She is trained.
No, It's OK.
Let's do the calculation.
This weapon has 13 bullets,  after
the motorcycle reload ....
a photo with him, an air
and leaving him 10 shots.
I killed him.  Yes, he did.
It was not.  RevГ­sate-neck.
How were  4 or 5 shots Jerry?
You wasted 40% of the ammunition
and you do not have anything.
Gave us some time to
cross the barrier.
you should give me that gun.  Find it.
Wait. Leave.
Perhaps scared  with the shooting.
Escape! Idiot!
Travelers not escape.
And now says that soldier?
He is not stupid fleeing.
What are you doing?  Search-ups.
Travel itinerary.
Go to the site.
- What?
Nothing.
Damn!
You okay?
Yes, I am well.
I am a little upset
because I was fired.
Tell me about your son.
His name is  Stevie, right?
How old?  -4 Years.
You like things  Army?
As toy  you bought? Yes ... As
Yes, no  I do not know.
Failed to work ....
I'm pretty useless.
I was a coward, left  pregnant
and alone ....
Huiste.  Yes, I fled.
Then you go back  Now?
What a surprise  Christmas? Yes
Your new husband will be there
and even bought him a gift.
What is this?  Tools.
What is your name?  Cutter-Sam.
Medideth Cole.
This does not work, I can
not  or send a message.
I can not sit  What can I do?
I have it here.  quГ­tate blood.
Come on!
I'm Molly. I Annabel.
you should see how these
fleeing here.
They seem a lot  cheap.
Lower the head rabbit.
He was not shot the lights.
This is good.
bullets, are leaving for us.
Use a flashlight.
Thank you. Take care.
He was so humble.
Please, you have something.
Sorry I do not speak Spanish.
Do you speak Spanish?
I should know  at school, but ....
A bucket?
What is this?
No Yes, but you are doing
continue to do so.
You can help! You know?
Want to help my baby?  Sure.
We make a barricade,  Swimming would
be better not to use it explode.
Does this help?
She relaxes.
Do not let me leave
like a hot potato.
Look. A tranquilizer.  -Thanks.
Got it.  I think I have!
Wrong. He left behind  gas tank.
You okay?
Sam?  Yes, we are well.
Coach Вї?  Yes, OK.
ВїRabbit?  -MuГ©rdeme.
Shen Вї?  His name is Desiree.
Shut up rabbit. I'm fine.
What lies behind?
We will see here.
The ladder is  until then, come on.
This is scary here.
It is a beautiful thing.
Take care.  Yes
there. Right there.
See the refrigerators?
There will be another.
How do you know?
-This is where I would be.
Is well covered.
Out  the line of fire.
You are a hunter  or something?
I am a Ranger.
- What?
Expert  Archery.
Have you heard of MessLands,  the
convention of video games?
Is not this game develops
in the forest?
Yes, but the soldiers  7 worlds,
and that's the idea.
In fact going to California
for a competition.
So what is  arc?
Yes, if I could take a bow
It is in my luggage.
Which are given  to use?
Yes, but in the game  People
are not objective.
These people are less  people.
Come, rest  a little.
Come on.
Is everything all right partner?
Sorry, the left alone.
Have a happy Christmas.
And greets rarito  rarito
who walks with you.
Archie fool anyone.
How many?  Seven-count.
Where are they?
This is us.
Three are here  the barn.
There is one for  refrigerators.
There are two and a coverage
the way here.
You missed one.
There was one that  for help.
No wonder they have  tried
to burn it here.
They are also afraid.
The fires can be seen from afar.
No, they are waiting for  return
the rest of the group.
Want to share.
- You know these idiots?
Out with a motorcycle by  once.
He said the groups and the
nomadic  that are local.
Most no longer binds  the leaves.
are in place for a while,  Fighting
for what they need,
food, gas, money,  women ....
and continue.
My name is never joined them,
was not his style.
I was afraid of these nomads.
We put on the defensive
until help arrives.
Someone will come for us
at some point, right?
No, our next stop should
be Picadelly, Texas ....
If we fail, we  we hold that time.
I listen  for a second?
Would not last two minutes
if they decide to attack.
And then the bus was not very  both the driver and Mr.
Champ?.
You are the reason why we  coach here!
We can bear!
- Give a street prostitute instead?
Excuse my language.
Picadelly was not  an official stop.
If you do not stop to think that we
elsewhere, for petrol or food.
The next stop is the official,
300 miles there.
This means that they do not know that
we lack even within 6 hours.
Yes, unless you agree  each
pilot in the state.
You are the expert,  What do we do?
It's a girl.
How do we know  toys wrapped in Ohio?
What do we do?
I told you.  Do not stop.
What are you doing,  a bath?
Damn man.
What did you see? "I did laugh.
Tempting.
What are you doing?
Nothing. Only drawing.
I do it to win  dinerillo extra.
Design graphic novels.
Can I see?  This is nothing, really.
I would like to see it.
No, it is not important.
It is something ....
A map.
Where are we here?
The nearest village
It is 45 miles away.
There is a road  southeast of here.
It is only 19 .... 20 miles away.
Want someone to run  20 miles
through the countryside
So a line in a  Map card ....
probably  The traffic is once a month.
Who are you?
I will.
I run.
Go to the stadium to see soccer and go to
meetings of parents do not mind, madam.
I participate in marathons
support for breast cancer
the leukemia  I can run.
In the streets the day
give people with water.
We are not talking  walk ....
You think I'm an idiot, Mr.
Yarbro? I do not know?
I think we can  stand in this place.
No, we can not sit.
Someone has to go out and get help,
- I'm going to go.
- I would say ....
Let me go.
Does the type of control of anger
it does not work, coach?
We can support  here.
We can not.
How do I go to these
idiots out there?
No, Sam,  is a bad idea ....
I can shoot a  arrow to a person ....
I can not.
An arrow, Sam?
Robin Hood worked.
Robin Hood was not about
psychopaths shooting.
You really think  Annabel can do?
Worth .... Yet  that girl out?
No, he was.
Do not waste your time,  Move Sam.
Sam Dale, care ....
Sam ....
Sam, not more  bright ideas.
You think I saw?
ВїVerte?
They showed  how?
Agree  security, for what?
For that?
Are walkie-talkie, I thought
that could be useful.
You two stop.
What  rescue my clothes?
I do not know, I thought  you
have something useful ....
Simply gym clothes  and
dirty underwear.
- Take, for when you leave.
- Thanks.
Illiterate, illegal y. ...  a lunatic.
They know they can not
do this, right?
I can not kill anyone.
If you, dear.  You are not so special.
Baby ....
- Do you serve?
- Yes,
perfect, thanks.
What the hell were you in the middle
nothing on the eve of Christmas?
Go to a funeral.
I am a single mother,  then ....
I do not want my children to travel,
Not so close to Christmas ....
at least we have  that bus.
His sister  have cancer?
If ....
My sister, my  mother, myself.
Breast cancer.
These are my girls.
- This is Gracy and this is Emma.
- They are precious.
so it will run.
Here ....
just in case  that .... You know?
Yes, I understand.
Hey, what happens ....  Not pairs.
It's something I learned from the convoys in Iraq.
Okay?
I feel so  there is past you.
Hey ....
- I brought him a flashlight.
- Thanks, I need it.
Also this dress.
In case you  to rob a bank?
Do not have a  Compass below.
You can read a  compass, Maudie?
If I were boss  the girls scouts.
This is for you,  from a friend.
Come Stallions,  Right?
You pray,  Mr. Yarbro?
Only sex.  overnight.
In the meantime.
It is Friday night.
Merry Christmas.
- Hello?
- Is the old tractor.
No form of  may go unnoticed?
Yes, but if you get caught,  you a.
Sam and I said ....
I can not do that.
I Maudie,  I can not kill anyone.
Look ....
This is unfair.
It is not correct,
but I am a mother,  I have
children, I can not die.
Do not let me die.
Not seen yet ....
Shoot!  Shoot!
Come on, shoot.
I can not.
- Come on.
- What is happening?
His Princess  will let die.
Tell him to shoot, say
you have to shoot.
Sam? ? Sam? Are two  the case.
Hell, they will come.
Sam care.
Will be successful.
Maudie succeed.
Come on, hurry up.
Thank you.
Okay, he did  you had to do.
Okay, okay ....  Sure.
She killed two  security.
I do not know,  perhaps
injuring another.
So are four,  maybe five.
If.
This ....
driver on the road,  Was
that your first ....
No.
It becomes easier,  Huh?
If.
Good
Mapping something.
Is it Maudie.
What do we do?
Nothing, he is running.
Going to get it or not.
Damn, that was cold.
My God.
PongГЎmosla  inside the car.
He said he did laugh.
We all tried.
How long  were together?
Three days.
Somehow, it seems  worse and
that were still unknown.
we went to Las Vegas ....
her, and would distribute letters
to work in a wedding chapel.
I think he knew  the fund
was not going to work.
Thank you.
Even with that?
Yes, but .... motherfucker.
What, you understand?
Yes, I think it is a  potato
launcher, right?
ВїLauncher potatoes?
You can say  potato in Spanish?
What is a pitcher  Potatoes?
I remember a boy  my block
used to make ....
basically put a pope, he  flammable put
something on the other side ....
E booooom.
All flammable  petrol?
No, we ....
Spray,  use spray.
First arrow,  Now potato cannon.
What follows,  an air gun?
I do not know these things
shoot anything.
Place nails  rocks, anything.
When we arrived at the  Spray?
Forget spray  hair, there ether.
It was very short, they must  create
it if they want to destroy the bike.
Son of a bitch.
Animals.
Come on.
- Go after that ....
- And you?
Where  is this son of a bitch.
Turn.
Do not shoot.
We are well.
We did.
Resist,  soldier. Resist.
I can not die ....
I have children ....
I have children.
Sorry.
Take that, stupid.
- I need this car.
- The keys are inside.
The more  escaped?
Around seven.  Seven.
ВїMeredith Cole?
It wound  but it is strong.
- You know?
- Try to find.
At the end of this  Double
Highway South,
There is a small town  10 or 20 miles,
call it from there.
Before being killed  for help.
The sun is coming out?
If women, possibly.
Come on, we  a lot of ground to cover.
How?
Six, eight ....
I do not know, maybe more.
ВїCole, what do you think?
- Run.
- You are wounded soldier ....
not reach  to 100 feet.
I,  the rest of you,
Give me the gun  and
a pair of molotovs.
- No, we a. ...
- Get out of here.
What, so they can  cazarnos
and kill us one by one?
- Coach?
- We can take it.
ВїDuke?
Annabel Вї?
I have two or three, but then
they have to do with the rest.
Do it.
We prepare.
Ani-le-li-jah ....
What does that mean?
Something that the Iraqis  say ....
in the middle of the danger you ask  God
for the fate of their compatriots.
Good luck, Sam.
The name?
This leads  one of the dead.
Do arrows?
Idiot.
Fire.
Die, you bastards.
- Duke?
- Got it.
Fuck you, Texas.
Coach ....
Help.
Here, motherfucker ....
should never return.
I hope he is  more ammunition ....
Huiremos not more,  coach.
Aguante.
ВїDuke?
Too late ....
Sam ....
You okay?
I've been better.
Come here.
Hello, Sergeant.
Mr. Vargas is in surgery,  but
they are optimistic ....
- Vargas Vargas  is a good man.
If ....
Look, sorry, not the sergeant
I said that I was hunting.
Sure.
I understand that it was
a very difficult night.
The hospital gave me
chills, then ....
His daughters are here.
- Do not stop, never stop.
- You want.
Thank you.
We will not give a minute?
Custard  is bullshit.
I talked to the doctors.
They want you to stay.
But I am convinced that you
strong enough to travel.
Thanks, Sarge.
As you know  I hate the
food in hospitals.
You will be handcuffed and taken to court
which will be tried for desertion.
The place, the wife of  civilians
who speak ....
is not what I know.
So he had to say?
Why not escape  is my business?
Personally ....
I think the master  deserved it.
But I do not give  those orders.
Dress, cover.
It is about 20 minutes before
they come to look.
Archie?
Merry Christmas, angel.
Travel by road?
In march, gentlemen.
- Do not stop.
Subtitles by
http://www.Downloadking2.Tk